Guide to the Campbell Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
Campbell Family Papers
1855-1972
RG 7
Yale University Divinity School Library
13
(31 boxes)
The papers document two generations of Baptist missionary effort in South China. Extensive biographical and autobiographical material gives insight into the personal lives of the Campbells. Conditions in China during World War II are reflected in the letters of Louise and Dorothy Campbell. The Campbells were a family of missionaries in China. George Campbell and his wife, Jennie Wortman Campbell served in South China (1887-1916). Four of their eight children continued missionary efforts. Louise Campbell, principal of the Kwong Yit Girls' School, Meihsien, Kwangtung Province, worked for 40 years among the Hakka tribespeople, as did her sister, Margaret Larue Campbell Burket and Margaret's husband, Everett S. Burket from 1916-1946. Dorothy McBride Campbell served in China from 1926-1944, as did David Miles Campbell from 1926-1942.
Campbell family
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the Campbell family
Biographical / Historical
The marriage of Jennie Wortman and George Campbell marked the beginning of two generations of Baptist missionary effort, first in the United States and later in China. The products of deeply religious families, both had decided independently to become missionaries prior to meeting. In turn, four of the couple's eight children continued the missionary efforts. As detailed biographical information regarding each member of this large family was prepared by Dorothy Campbell and is available in Series IV, folders 3-12, only brief sketches will be given here. (In addition, autobiographical information regarding Jennie W. Campbell and Dorothy M. Campbell is located in Series III, folders 4, 8, 15, 16, and 17.)
Born in less at St. Charles, Illinois, George Campbell spent most of his boyhood and early youth in Delavan, Illinois where his father was a Baptist minister from 1872 to 1885. St. Charles, Illinois is located thirty miles west of Chicago. Delavan, Illinois is thirty miles south of Peoria. Both parents, Thomas Philpot Campbell and Marian Packer Campbell, were educated, transplanted Easterners.(It is interesting to note that Thomas Philpot Campbell offered himself for missionary service, ultimately to be rejected on the grounds of his wife's poor health. She outlived him by twenty years.) George, their only son, graduated from Colgate University, (though some sources indicate Colgate University, Hamilton, N.Y., where others state Hamilton College), his father's alma mater, and Morgan Park Baptist Theological Seminary. He married Jennie Wortman in 1882, as previously noted.
Jennie Wortman was born in a log cabin in Van Wert, Ohio in l863. Shortly thereafter, her father, James Wortman, died in the Civil War. Her mother, Mary Larue Wortman, an Ohio native, remarried in 1868 to widower Reuben B. Wood, a Baptist deacon. This merger created a large family: three Wortman children and seven Wood children, in addition to two children of Mary and Reuben Wood. Jennie Wortman received her teaching certificate at the age of fourteen and considered becoming a medical missionary. Two years later she attended Mt. Carroll Seminary for Girls in Illinois, where her schoolmate Elia Campbell introduced her to Elia's brother George.
Following their marriage in 1882, George and Jennie Campbell served as home missionaries in the North West Territory from 1882-1885, and at Tecumsah, Nebraska from 1885-1887. In that year, they left for China with their three small children, Five more children were born between that time and 1901.
The couple served in South China from less to 1900, 1908 to 1912, and from 1914 to 1916. An eight year span, 1900 - 1908, was spent in missionary activity on the West Coast of the United States. Following her husband's death in 1927, Jennie Campbell returned to China where she remained until 1933. She died in 1939 at the home of her son, Kenneth.
Louise Campbell (1883-1968) graduated from Occidental College, Los Angeles, California, in 1928 and served as a China missionary for forty years. Her work centered on the Hakkas, hill people of the region, and as principal of the Kwong Yit Girls' School, Meihaien, Kwingtung Province.
Miriam Elizabeth Campbell (1885- c.1972) had some musical education, became a nurse, and served in France during World War One. She married Captain Edward L. Joyce, whom she met in Europe. The couple had two sons, one of whom was killed in World War Two. She lived in Toledo, Ohio from 1919 to 1944, at which time she moved to California.
Paul Wortman Campbell (1887-1966) attended the Mt. Herman School, Northfield, Massachusetts, and spent most of his life as a realtor in Eugene, Oregon. He married Lanna Mallet in 1918, and the couple had three sons.
Thomas Packer Campbell (1889-1951) also attended the Mt. Hermon School, Northfield, Massachusetts. He later enrolled at Linfield College, McMinnville, Oregon, and studied Forestry at Oregon Agricultural College, Corvallis. He spent much of his life in the Navy, serving in both World Wars. In 1918 he married Lola Finley, and the couple had three daughters.
Margaret Larue Campbell (1891-1952) graduated from Linfield College in 1913 and married her classmate, Everett S. Burket, the following year. In 1916, the couple sailed for China, where they worked among the Hakkas until their retirement in 1946. They had four children.
Kenneth Malcolm Campbell (1896-c.1973) attended the China Inland Mission School for Boys, Chefoo, North China (where he was a classmate of Thornton Wilder), and Linfield College, and enlisted in the Navy during World War One. He spent much of his life as a teacher and farmer in Washington. His wife, Bodil Weil, was also a teacher. They had four children.
Dorothy McBride Campbell (1898-1972) graduated from Linfield College around 1920, Seattle General Hospital School of Nursing, Class of 1923, and the Bible Institute of Los Angeles. In 1926 she left for China where she served until 1944. At that time she became a nurse in New York City, where she pursued her interests in writing and psychology by taking courses at Columbia University.
David Miles Campbell (1901-c.1972) attended Linfield College for two years, the Bible Institute of Los Angeles from 1922 to 1934, and graduated from Occidental College in 1926. He served as a China missionary from 1926-1942. From 1942 to 1944 he was interpreter for Chinese troops for General Joseph Stilwell. After the war, he became a contractor in Eugene, Oregon. In 1957, he moved to Southern California where he retired in 1964. He married Bessie Mae Gillis in 1936. The couple, divorced in 1962, had three children.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, 1880s-1972
Diaries and Notebooks, 1855-1968
Writings, 1880-1972
Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1868-1972
The papers, which span the years 1855 to 1972, chronicle two generations of Baptist missionary effort in South China, and afford glimpses into the generations which preceded this endeavor. It should be noted that the Papers generally tend to document most heavily the lives of George and Jennie Campbell, and their daughters, Louise and Dorothy. Some members of the family are represented by a minimal amount of material.
Correspondence, the first series in the Papers, spans four generations, from George and Jennie Campbell's parents to their grandchildren. However, the bulk of the material was written by members of the two missionary generations.
Each of the eight Campbell children is represented in this series. The letters of Kenneth Campbell to his parents while he attended the China Inland Mission Boy's School at Chefoo, North China from 1909 to 1912 are of particular interest. Later letters of Louise and Dorothy Campbell reflect war-time conditions in China Louise, Miriam, Kenneth, Dorothy, and David exchanged letters frequently in their old age.
Diaries and Notebooks, the largest series in the Campbell Family Papers, is composed of the material of five individuals: (1) Thomas Philpot Campbell - one diary, kept from 1855 to 1857, which contains accounts of his travels. (2) George Campbell - many diaries, notebooks, autograph books, etc. These sources chronicle the missionary's life from his youth in Illinois, to China, and old age. The material spans the years from 1874 to 1927. (3) Jennie W. Campbell - several diaries, guest books, birthday books, etc. Her earliest diary, written from 1881 to 1882 while at Mt. Carroll Seminary for Girls in Illinois, may be of particular interest. Her material dates from 1879 to 1939, although there is a gap in diary keeping from 1882 to 1927. (4) Louise Campbell - extensive diary kept from 1895 to 1967 with few interruptions. Notebooks, date books, account books, etc. comprise the remainder of her material. (5) Dorothy Campbell - extensive personal diaries and notebooks recorded from 1908 to 1966, with few exceptions.
Writings, the third series, is also the smallest. Autobiographical accounts of Jennie and Dorothy Campbell are of interest. The bulk of the material in this series was penned by Dorothy Campbell in conjunction with her continuing education in psychology and writing.
All the material is in manuscript form, with the exception of two copies of a 1957 Church publication which contains writings by both Miriam C. Joyce and David Campbell.
Personal Items and Memorabilia, the final series, contains a variety of material. Extensive biographical material, including the Genealogy of the Descendents of George and Jennie Campbell prepared by David Campbell, is located at the beginning of the series.
The material of George Campbell includes several folders pertaining to the genealogy of the Campbell family and development of the milk goal industry--both of his retirement hobbies.
A small amount of printed material is housed within this section. A 1929 Chinese piracy incident, which directly involved Jennie, Louise, and Dorothy Campbell, made national headlines and is located with other over-sized material.
A separate section of Photographs contains material dating from the Civil War to the 1970's. Photographs of George and Jennie Campbell prior to their courtship and scenes of China are of special interest. Life at the China Inland Mission School in Chefoo, North China between 1909 and 1912 is also depicted. Thornton Wilder, noted author and playwright, is in one of the group photos.
Arrangement
I. Correspondence, 1800s-1972
II. Diaries and Notebooks, 1855-1968
III. Writings, 1880-1972
IV. Personal Items and Memorabilia, 1868-1972
Missions -- China; Missions; World War, 1939-1945; Educators; Missionaries; Nurses; Burket, Margaret Larue Campbell, 1896-1973; Campbell, David Miles, 1901-1972; Campbell, Dorothy McBride, 1898-1972; Campbell, George, 1858-; Campbell, Jennie Wortman, 1863-1939; Campbell, Louise, 1883-1968; Campbell family; Kwong Yit Girls' School
- Correspondence, 1880s-1972; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Material in this series is arranged chronologically by generation. The letters of George Campbell have also been given a topical arrangement. The correspondence of the eight Campbell children is also filed chronologically; the letters of Louise, the eldest child, appear first, while those of David, the youngest child, are last. Letters written by their spouses and children immediately follow. Material written by the Campbells or their relatives is filed according to writer. Letters to the Campbells from various sources outside the family are inter-filed chronologically with the letters which they wrote. (For example, Louise Campbell's file contains the letters which she wrote, and those which she received from people outside her family.)
  - Marian P. Campbell to George and Jennie Campbell, 1902, 1905, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mary W. Wood to Jennie W. Campbell, family, 1899-1900, 1903 1904 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mary W. Wood to Jennie W. Campbell, family, 1905-1906 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mary W. Wood to Jennie W. Campbell, family; incl. note from "Carey" (cousin?), 1907, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mary W. Wood to Jennie W. Campbell, family, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mary W. Wood to Jennie W. Campbell, family, Margaret, 1911-1913 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mary W. Wood to Jennie W. Campbell, family; note from Lillian Whitman to JWC enclosed, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mary W. Wood to Jennie W. Campbell, family, Dorothy; incl. letter from nephew Lester, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Elia Campbell Whitman to Paul Campbell, Melvin L. Wortman to Geo. and Jennie Campbell, 1893, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mary Campbell to unnamed friends, 1916, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - George Campbell to family, 1901, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - George Campbell to family, 1911 Jan-May (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - George Campbell to family, 1911 Jun-Dec (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - George Campbell to family, 1912-1913 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - George Campbell to family, Elia, 1914-1916, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - George Campbell to family, 1921-1926 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - George Campbell to family, 1927, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - George Campbell - report letter, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - George Campbell re: Agriculture from: University of Puerto Rico, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - George Campbell to Postmaster at Swatow, China, c. 1880'S, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - George Campbell to Editor of The Standard (Chicago);Dr. Foster; Pastors of the Baptist Churches of the Northwest, c. 1914, 1927
  - George Campbell to/from U.S. Dep't. of Agriculture, 1909, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - George Campbell to/from U.S. Dep't. of Agriculture, 1911-1914 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - George Campbell to/from U.S. Dep't. of Agriculture, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - George Campbell re: Genealogy, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - George Campbell re: Genealogy to/from: Eugenics Record Office, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - George Campbell re: Genealogy, 1915, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - George Campbell re: Genealogy, 1922-1924 May (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - George Campbell re: Genealogy, 1924 Jul-Oct (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - George Campbell re: Genealogy, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - George Campbell re: Genealogy, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - George Campbell re: death of Mary Campbell, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - George Campbell from "All Hakka Convention" re: death of Elia Campbell Whitman, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Jennie Campbell - Copy book of letters, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Jennie Campbell - extracts, notes and typed copies from her copy book, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Jennie Campbell to family, 1896-1897, 1902, 1911,1919 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - See also: Kenneth Campbell, Series I, Folder No. 155
  - Jennie Campbell to family, c. 1922, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Jennie Campbell to family, 1925, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Jennie Campbell to family, 1928, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Jennie Campbell to family, 1930-1932 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Jennie Campbell to family, 1934-1937 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Jennie Campbell to family, 1938-1939, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Jennie Campbell from Callie Wortman (sister), c. 1902-1905 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Jennie Campbell to E. Powell of the China Inland Mission School re: dog bite inflicted on Kenneth Campbell, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Jennie Campbell re: deaths of George Campbell, and "Dad Wortman", 1927, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Misc: M.E. Adkins to "Co-Workers"--probably George and/or Jennie Campbell - re: Kansas City Convention, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Louise Campbell, 1910-1917 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Louise Campbell, 1920-1924 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Louise Campbell, 1924-1927 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Louise Campbell, 1928-1929 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Louise Campbell, 1930,1933, 1935 1936 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Louise Campbell, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Louise Campbell, 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Dorothy Campbell from Edith Traver with 2 articles enclosed, c. 1940's (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Louise Campbell, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Louise Campbell, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Louise Campbell, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Louise Campbell, 1945 Jan-May (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Louise Campbell, 1945 Jun-Dec (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Louise Campbell, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Louise Campbell, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Louise Campbell, 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Louise Campbell, 1951 Jan-Jul (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Louise Campbell, 1951 Aug-Dec (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Louise Campbell, 1952 Jan-Mar (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Louise Campbell, 1952 Apr-May (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Louise Campbell, 1952 Jun (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Louise Campbell, 1952 Jul-Aug (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Louise Campbell, 1952 Sep-Dec (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Louise Campbell, 1953 Jan-Mar (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Louise Campbell, 1953 Apr-Jun (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Louise Campbell, 1953 Jul-Sep (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Louise Campbell, 1954 Jan-May (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Louise Campbell, 1954 Aug-Dec (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Louise Campbell, 1955 Jan-Mar (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Louise Campbell, 1955 May-Aug (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Louise Campbell, 1955 Sep-Dec, n.m. (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Louise Campbell, 1956 Jan-Apr (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Louise Campbell, 1956 May-Sep (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Louise Campbell, 1956 Oct-Dec (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Louise Campbell, 1958 Jul-Sep (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Louise Campbell, 1958 Oct-Dec (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Louise Campbell, 1959 Jan-May (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Louise Campbell, 1959 Jun-Dec (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Louise Campbell, 1960 Jan-Mar (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Louise Campbell, 1960 Apr-Aug (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Louise Campbell, 1960 Oct-Dec (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Louise Campbell, 1961 Feb-Apr (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Louise Campbell, 1961 May-Jul (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Louise Campbell, 1961 Aug-Nov, n.m. (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Louise Campbell, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Louise Campbell, 1963 Jan-May (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Louise Campbell, 1963 Jun-Dec (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Louise Campbell, 1964, n.m. (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Louise Campbell, 1965 Mar-Aug (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Louise Campbell, 1965 Oct-Dec, n.m. (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Louise Campbell, 1966 Jan-Apr (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Louise Campbell, 1966 May-Jul (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Louise Campbell, 1966 Sep-Nov, n.m. (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Louise Campbell, 1967 Jan-Apr (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Louise Campbell, 1967 May-Sep (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Louise Campbell, 1967 Oct-Dec, n.m. (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Louise Campbell, 1968, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Louise Campbell - postcards to Dorothy Campbell, 1951-1967, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Louise Campbell to/from: Maurice Jeanson, U.S. Dep't. of Agriculture re: seeds, 1917, 1924, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Letters of Condolence re: Louise Campbell, A-C, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Letters of Condolence re: Louise Campbell, D-H, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Letters of Condolence re: Louise Campbell, J-Z, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce re: death of her mother; telegram re: death of her father, 1927, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1948-1952 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1953 Jan-Jul (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, (1953?) (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, (1955?) (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1963 Jan-Feb (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1963 Mar-Apr (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1963 May (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, 1964, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, c. 1964-1972 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - Miriam Campbell Joyce, c. 1964-1972 (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - James C. Joyce (son) to Miriam Campbell Joyce, Dorothy Campbell, "Kay", 1934, 1958, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - Paul Campbell, 1908,1910-1911,1913 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Paul Campbell, 1925,1927, 1933 1935, 1942,1952, 1955-1956, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Paul Campbell: Letter re: Family Reunion held at Eugene, Ore., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Lenna M. Campbell (Mrs. Paul)-incl. "round-robin" family letter, Philip Campbell (son), 1933-1938, ca.1955, 1958-1959, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Lenna M. Campbell (Mrs. Paul), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Thomas Campbell, 1920,1922, 1924,1945, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Thomas Campbell, 1951-1952, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Lola F. Campbell (Mrs. Thomas), with excerpts from letters of Louise C. Turcotte, Dorothy Campbell, Louise Campbell, Lola F. Campbell (See also: Bio. of T.P. Campbell in PIM), 1927, c. 1940's, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Louise Campbell Turcotte (daughter) and children, 1952, 1966, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Jean Campbell Conley (daughter), 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Margaret Campbell Burket, 1910, 1917-1919 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Margaret Campbell Burket, 1925, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Margaret Campbell Burket, 1931,1935, 1939,1945 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Margaret Campbell Burket, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Everett S. Burket, 1927, 1928, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Telegram re: death of Margaret Campbell Burket, letters of George and Stanley Burket (sons), 1952, 1955-1959 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1909 Feb-May (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1909 Jun-Aug (Box 8, Folder 140)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1909 Sep-Nov (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1910 Feb-Apr (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1910 May-Jun (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1910 Jul-Aug (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1910 Sep (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1910 Oct-Nov (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1911 Jan, Apr (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1911 May-Jun (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1911 Jul-Aug (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1911 Sep-Oct (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1911 Nov-Dec (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1912 Jan-Mar (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1912 Apr-May (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1912 Jun-Jul (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Kenneth Campbell, 1912 Aug-Sep (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Kenneth Campbell: Lists of boys, adults, and subjects mentioned in his letters to home from, 1972,1909-1912 (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, incl. note by Jennie Campbell, 1923-1938 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, 1951-1960 (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, 1964 Jan-Mar (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, 1964 Apr-Dec (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, 1965 Jan-May (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Kenneth and Bodil Campbell, 1970, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 166)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 167)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1925 Feb-Jun (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1925 Jul-Aug (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1925 Sep-Nov (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1926 Feb-Jun (Box 9, Folder 171)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1926 Jul-Nov (Box 9, Folder 172)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 173)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 174)
  - Dorothy Campbell 1929, c. 1926-1929 (Box 9, Folder 175)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1931-1932 (Box 9, Folder 176)
  - Dorothy Campbell 1933, c. 1933 (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Dorothy Campbell, 1936 Jan-Jul (Box 9, Folder 180)